(Leonard:)Anyone else see the flaw in this plan?
(Raj:)We need a social catalyst.
(Leonard:)Like what?
We can't get 15-year-old girls drunk.
- Or can we?
- No, we can't.
(Howard:)I don't think you mean we can't.
I think you mean we shouldn't.
(Sheldon:)Hey, Howard, you're a Jew.
(Sheldon:)If there was another Wailing Wall
exactly like the one in Jerusalem...
(Sheldon:)...but close to taco stands
and cheap prescription drugs...
...would you still wail at it?
(Sheldon:)Okay, it's definitely me.
(Leonard:)We cannot leave this to chance.
Let's pick a girl...
(Leonard:)...and figure out
how to get her with Dennis.
How about that one?
(Howard:)Uh-uh. I know the type. Cheerleader,
student council, goes out with jocks.
Won't look at anybody
in the gifted program.
If she does agree to go out,
it turns out to be a setup.
You're in your mom's car with your pants off
while the whole football team laughs.
- Are you crying?
- No, I have allergies.